Contact

7862469402 (Mobile) edurovich@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ elizabethdurovich (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Customer Service Microsoft Excel

Languages

Spanish

Certifications

TNCC

PALS Healthcare Provider
Registered Professional Nurse
BLS Healthcare Provider
CEN

Honors-Awards

Dean's List Non-RN Scholarship Award

Elizabeth Durovich MSN RN PMHNP-BC CEN

Psychiatric Nurse Practitioner New York, New York

Summary

Psychiatric Nurse Practitioner and Emergency Department
Registered Nurse with 8+ years experience in clinical settings
including training and education in the Trauma/Emergency Medicine
field and Psychiatric Services providing nursing care to diverse
populations, including specialization in Spanish-speaking patients.
Trained Sexual Assault Forensic Examiner. Nursing educator for
undergraduate curriculum and NCLEX-RN

Experience

Mental Health Providers of Western Queens, Inc.
Psychiatric Nurse Practitioner
December 2019 - Present (6 months)
Queens, New York, United States

Outpatient Mental Health Services for Adults

Borough of Manhattan Community College Adjunct Professor January 2020 - Present (5 months) New York

Mount Sinai Queens Sexual Assault Forensic Examiner | Staff RN July 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months) Astoria, New York

Per Diem - SAFE at BI, MSH, MSQ

Montefiore Health System
Emergency Room RN - Pediatrics
August 2015 - Present (4 years 10 months)
Bronx, New York

Per Diem - CHAM, Childrens Hospital at Montefiore

Wyzant

Tutor - Nursing

May 2014 - January 2020 (5 years 9 months)

www.wyzant.com/tutors/elizabethd

NYC Health + Hospitals
Psychiatric Nurse Practitioner Intern
August 2018 - June 2019 (11 months)

New York, New York

Bellevue Hospital Center

Northwell Health Emergency Room RN September 2015 - April 2019 (3 years 8 months) New York

Part-time, Preceptor

St. Barnabas Hospital
Staff RN - Emergency Department
September 2014 - January 2018 (3 years 5 months)
Bronx, New York

Per Diem

East Orange General Hospital - 300 Central Avenue Intensive Care Nurse
August 2016 - December 2017 (1 year 5 months)
East Orange, New Jersey

Per Diem

NYC Health and Hospitals Corporation Staff RN - Emergency Department November 2014 - September 2015 (11 months) Elmhurst Hospital Center - Queens, NY

Level I Trauma Center

TakeLessons
Tutor - Multiple Subjects
January 2014 - May 2015 (1 year 5 months)
New York, NY

Visiting Nurse Service of New York

Page 2 of 4

RN - Community Health Educator and Case Management August 2014 - November 2014 (4 months)

New York, NY

NYC Health and Hospitals Corporation Nurse Intern - Adult Emergency Services June 2013 - September 2014 (1 year 4 months) Bellevue Hospital Center - New York, NY

DogVacay
Professional Trainer and Sitter
January 2013 - August 2014 (1 year 8 months)
New York, NY

Healthcare Innovation & Technology Lab Administrative Support Specialist January 2013 - July 2014 (1 year 7 months) New York, NY

City University of New York
Tutor - Nursing
January 2014 - May 2014 (5 months)
Borough of Manhattan Community College, New York, NY

Enhancing critical thinking skills and case management practices by using the nursing process and practical skills of therapeutic interventions at the fundamentals and medical-surgical level

Revolution Prep SAT/ACT Proctor January 2013 - May 2014 (1 year 5 months) New York, NY

Caption House
Transcriptionist
January 2006 - December 2007 (2 years)

Education

City University of New York-Hunter College

Master of Science (M.S.), Psychiatric/Mental Health Nurse/ Nursing · (2017 - 2019)

City University of New York-Hunter College Bachelor in Nursing, Nursing · (2014 - 2016)

Borough of Manhattan Community College Associate of Applied Science, Nursing · (2012 - 2014)